Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Donald W. Taylor as dean, 1969-1976; Accession 2004-A-140
  - Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 590)
  - Advisory Committee of the Graduate School
    - 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 591 - 594)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 595)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 596 - 597)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 598)
  - Graduate School Advisory Committee Student Members, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 599)
  - Graduate School Advisory Committee Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 600 - 601)
  - Advisory Committee of the Graduate School (Box 12, Folder 602)
  - Discipline (Box 12, Folder 603)
  - Memoranda to the Members of the Executive Committee of the Graduate School, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 604)
  - Meetings of the Executive Committee of the Graduate School, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 605)
  - Executive Committee of the Graduate School (Box 12, Folder 606)
  - Letters for the Executive Committee of the Graduate School (Box 12, Folder 607)
  - Executive Committee of the Graduate School, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 608 - 613)
  - Senior Appointments Material, 1970- (Box 12, Folder 614)
  - Biological Sciences Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 615)
  - Social Sciences Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 616)
  - Physical Sciences Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 617)
  - Humanities Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 618)
  - Senior Appointments Committee Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 619)
  - Senior Appointments Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 620)
  - Physical Sciences Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 621)
  - Humanities Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 622)
  - Social Sciences Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 623)
  - Biological Sciences Senior Appointments Committee Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 624)
  - Degree Committees, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 625)
  - Citations for Retiring Faculty, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 626 - 627)
  - Graduate School Faculty Meeting
    - 1972 Jun 2 (Box 12, Folder 628)
    - 1972 Mar 3 (Box 12, Folder 629)
    - 1971 Dec 3 (Box 12, Folder 630)
    - 1971 Jun 4 (Box 12, Folder 631)
    - 1971 Oct 8 (Box 12, Folder 632)
    - 1971 Jun 4 (Box 12, Folder 633)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 634)
  - Leaves of Absence Denied or Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 635)
  - Leaves of Absence Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 636)
  - Requests for Leaves of Absence, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 637)
  - Leaves of Absence Denied or Withdrawn, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 638)
  - Leaves of Absence Approved, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 639)
  - The Belief Dilemma Resolver - R.P. Abelson (Box 13, Folder 640)
  - A Computer Simulation of Community Referendum Controversies - R.P Abelson (Box 13, Folder 641)
  - A Computer Program Which Assesses the Credibility of Assertions - J.D. Carroll (Box 13, Folder 642)
  - Pretending to Use (or to Be) a Computer as a Strategy in Teaching - P.C. Berry (Box 13, Folder 643)
  - Simulation: An Introduction to a New Technology - E. Bogdanoff, et al (Box 13, Folder 644)
  - An Investigation of Sequential Search Algorithms - H. Beiman, et al (Box 13, Folder 645)
  - Classification of Electrocardiograms Using the Polynomial Discriminant Method of Pattern Classification (Box 13, Folder 646)
  - Heuristics in Job Shop Scheduling - W.S. Gere, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 647)
  - The Simulation of Verbal Learning Behavior - E.A. Feigenbaum, Consultant (Box 13, Folder 648)
  - Artificial Intelligence: Themes in the Second Decade - E.A. Feigenbaum (Box 13, Folder 649)
  - Generalization of an Elementary Perceiving and Memorizing Machine - E.A. Feigenbaum (Box 13, Folder 650)
  - Information Processing Theory of Verbal Learning - E.A. Feigenbaum (Box 13, Folder 651)
  - Computer Programs for the Analysis of Consumer Panel Data - R.E. Frank (Box 13, Folder 652)
  - Computers in Behavioral Science - Performance of a Reading Task by an Elementary Perceiving and Memorizing Machine - E.A. Feigenbaum, et al (Box 13, Folder 653)
  - Forgetting in an Association Memory - E.A. Feigenbaum, et al (Box 13, Folder 654)
  - A Theory of the Serial Position Effect - E.A. Feigenbaum (Box 13, Folder 655)
  - Instructions for "The Railroad Game" (Box 13, Folder 656)
  - Profile Analysis Revisited: A Heuristic Approach - B. Kleinmuntz (Box 13, Folder 657)
  - A Study of Technological Innovation - The Evolution of Digital Computers (Box 13, Folder 658)
  - Simulation of the Firm - K.J. Cohen (Box 13, Folder 659)
  - Simulation and a Theory of Organizational Behavior - G.P.E. Clarkson (Box 13, Folder 660)
  - Management Games, Information Processing, and Control - K.J. Cohen, et al (Box 13, Folder 661)
  - Computer Models in Dynamic Economics - K.J. Cohen, et al (Box 13, Folder 662)
  - The C.I.T. Management Game - R.M. Cyert, et al (Box 13, Folder 663)
  - Consistency of Performance in Simulated Situations - N. Frederiksen (Box 13, Folder 664)
  - Management Decision Simulation for the LGP-1930 Digital Computer - W.D. Drake (Box 13, Folder 665)
  - An Information-Processing Model of One Kind of Problem-Solving - E.S. Johnson (Box 13, Folder 666)
  - The Processing of Clinical Information by Man and Machine - E.S. Johnson (Box 13, Folder 667)
  - Personality Test Interpretation by Computer and Clinician - B. Kleinmuntz (Box 13, Folder 668)
  - Simulated Problem-Solving: A Summary of a Model, and Some Representative Data - E.S. Johnson (Box 13, Folder 669)
  - Elements of a Theory of Human Problem Solving - A. Newell, et al (Box 13, Folder 670)
  - Organizational Psychology - H.J. Leavitt, et al (Box 13, Folder 671)
  - Computer Simulation of Concept Attainment - C.I. Hoviland (Box 13, Folder 673)
  - A Computer Approach to Content Analysis - Studies Using the General Inquirer System - P.J. Stone, et al (Box 13, Folder 674)
  - A Formal Deductive Problem-Solving System - J.P. Quinlan, et al (Box 13, Folder 675)
  - Some Characteristics of Human Information Processing - C. Hunt, et al (Box 13, Folder 676)
  - Executive Action Simulation - L.W. Herron (Box 13, Folder 677)
  - Validation Studies of the Inter-Nation Simulation - C.F. Hermann, et al (Box 13, Folder 678)
  - Computer Simulation of Concept Attainment - C.I. Hoviland (Box 13, Folder 679)
  - A Comparison of Memory Allocation Algorithms in a Logical Pattern Reorganizer - G. Diehr, et al (Box 13, Folder 680)
  - Hunt - Computer Course (Box 13, Folder 681)
  - Scientific American - Metabolism of a Camel (Box 13, Folder 682)
  - Motivation Inherent in Information Processing and Action - J.W. Hunt (Box 13, Folder 683)
  - The Study of Intelligent Behavior - G.A. Miller (Box 13, Folder 684)
  - Efficient and Viable Organization Forms - J. Marschak (Box 13, Folder 685)
  - The Digital Computer as a Musical Instrument - M.V. Mathews (Box 13, Folder 686)
  - Think (Box 13, Folder 687)
  - A Single Equation Model for Estimating Short Term Price and Dealing Effects in Selected Market Segment for a Frequently Purchased Computer Product - W.F. Massy (Box 13, Folder 688)
  - A Theoretical Model for Purchase Timing - W.F. Massy, et al (Box 13, Folder 689)
  - Paper Presented at the Joint IRE-AIEE-ALM Computer Conference: Los Angeles, California -, 1961 May 9-11 (Box 13, Folder 690)
  - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society - Memory and Learning (Box 13, Folder 691)
  - A Logical Machine for Measuring Problem Solving Ability - C.R. Langmuir (Box 13, Folder 692)
  - Material Accompanying the Paper - On Games The Simulate Complex Conflicts - B. Lieberman (Box 13, Folder 693)
  - Packaged Logic for Computers (Box 13, Folder 694)
  - Heuristic Decision Procedures, Open Constraints, and the Structure of Ill-Defined Problems - W.R. Reitman (Box 13, Folder 695)
  - Programming Intelligent Problem-Solvers - W.R. Reitman (Box 13, Folder 696)
  - The Uses of Plato (Box 13, Folder 697)
  - Quantitative Psychiatric Classification Procedures - J.E. Overall, et al (Box 13, Folder 698)
  - Conditional Probability Program for Diagnosis of Thyroid Function - J.E. Overall, et al (Box 13, Folder 699)
  - Computer Simulation of Cognition Balancing - P. Oltman, et al (Box 13, Folder 700)
  - The Simulation of Human Thought - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 701)
  - Empirical Explorations of the Logic Theory Machine: A Case Study in Heuristic - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 702)
  - Programming the Logic Theory Machine - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 703)
  - The Logic Theory Machine: A Complex Information Processing System - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 704)
  - A Variety of Intelligent Learning in a General Problem Solver - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 705)
  - Report on a General Problem-Solving Program - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 706)
  - The Analysis of Proximities: Multidimensional Scaling with an Unknown Distance Function - R.N. Shepard (Box 14, Folder 707)
  - Computer Simulation of Human Thinking and Problem Solving - H.A. Simon, et al (Box 14, Folder 708)
  - What Have Computers To Do With Management? - H.A. Simon, et al (Box 14, Folder 709)
  - A Command Structure for Complex Information Processing - J.C. Shaw, et al (Box 14, Folder 710)
  - IBM Journal of Research and Development (Box 14, Folder 711)
  - Simulation of Individual and Group Behavior - G.P.E. Clarkson, et al (Box 14, Folder 712)
  - Experiments with a Heuristic Compiler - H.A. Simon (Box 14, Folder 713)
  - Cognitive Processes in Solving Algebra Word Problems - J.M. Paige, et al (Box 14, Folder 714)
  - IBM Journal of Research and Development (Box 14, Folder 715)
  - Simulation of Cognitive Processes: A Report on the Summer Research Training Institute, - H.A. Simon, et al, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 716)
  - Pattern Recognition and Learning - O.G. Selfridge (Box 14, Folder 717)
  - An Elementary Pattern Inspection, Generalization, Recognition, and Abstraction Machine (EPIGRAM) - R.N. Shepard (Box 14, Folder 718)
  - Heuristic Problem Solving: The Next Advance in Operations Research - H.A. Simon, et al (Box 14, Folder 719)
  - Computer Simulation of Human Thinking and Problem Solving - H.A. Simon, et al (Box 14, Folder 720)
  - Some Studies in Machine Learning Using Game of Checkers II: Recent Progress - A.L. Samuel (Box 14, Folder 721)
  - Aggregation of Variables in Dynamic Systems - H.A. Simon, et al (Box 14, Folder 722)
  - Information Processing Language V Manual - Section 1. The Elements of IPL Programming - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 723)
  - Elements of a Theory of Human Problem Solving - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 724)
  - Computer Simulation of Human Thinking - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 725)
  - Report on the Algorithmic Language ALGOL 60 - P. Naur, et al (Box 14, Folder 726)
  - Information Processing Language V Manual - Section II. Programmers' Reference Manual - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 727)
  - Computer Simulation of Human Thinking and Problem Solving - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 728)
  - The Simulation of Human Thought - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 729)
  - Empirical Explorations of the Logic Theory Machine: A Case Study in Heuristic - A. Newell, et al (Box 14, Folder 730)
  - Personal Journal - D.W. Taylor (Box 14, Folder 731)
  - Approaches to Yale University (Box 14, Folder 732)
  - Cost of Education 681A-1935-1976840 (Box 14, Folder 733)
  - Financial Aid by Department (Box 14, Folder 734)
  - Financial Aid - Information Given to Ralph Burr and Robert O'Conner, 1969 December (Box 14, Folder 735)
  - Graduate Faculty Meeting, 1970 February 27 (Box 14, Folder 736)
  - Financial Aid, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 737 - 738)
  - Financial Aid - Information Given to Robert O'Conner, 1970 April 22 (Box 14, Folder 739)
  - Commitment of Fellowships Funds, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 740)
  - Analyses of Fellowship Offers by Department -, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 741)
  - Division Totals (Box 14, Folder 742)
  - Publications Concerning Financial Aid (Box 14, Folder 743)
  - Financial Aid - Details for Individual Departments, 1969 December (Box 14, Folder 744)
  - Cost of Education - Mar-Jun (Box 14, Folder 745)
  - Chemistry, 1970 March 2 (Box 15, Folder 746)
  - Chemistry Financial Aid (Box 15, Folder 747)
  - Financial Aid - Students Not Registered, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 748)
  - Analysis of Students Declining Admission (Box 15, Folder 749)
  - Admit Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 750)
  - Admit Letters (Box 15, Folder 751)
  - Some Aspects and Implications of Financial Need Analysis for Post-Baccalaureate Study - J.L. Bowman (Box 15, Folder 752)
  - The Financial Support of Graduate Students at Yale - Task Force on Fellowship and Financial Aid - Graduate-Professional Student Senate, 1972 January (Box 15, Folder 753)
  - Analysis of Financial Aid, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 754)
    - Mc (Box 15, Folder 755)
    - N (Box 15, Folder 756)
    - O (Box 15, Folder 757)
    - P (Box 15, Folder 758)
    - Q (Box 15, Folder 759)
    - R (Box 15, Folder 760)
    - S (Box 15, Folder 761)
    - T (Box 15, Folder 762)
    - U (Box 15, Folder 763)
    - V (Box 15, Folder 764)
    - W - 24 (Box 15, Folder 765)
    - XYZ (Box 15, Folder 766)
  - Grades - Reported Departmentally and Undergrad Courses - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 767)
  - Grades Received After Oct 1, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 768)
    - G (Box 15, Folder 769)
    - F (Box 15, Folder 770)
    - E (Box 15, Folder 771)
    - I (Box 15, Folder 772)
    - J (Box 15, Folder 773)
    - K (Box 15, Folder 774)
    - M (Box 15, Folder 775)
    - B (Box 15, Folder 776)
    - C (Box 15, Folder 777)
  - Extensions for Submission of Grades, 1965 June (Box 16, Folder 778)
    - L (Box 16, Folder 779)
    - H (Box 16, Folder 780)
    - D (Box 16, Folder 781)
    - A (Box 16, Folder 782)
    - B (Box 16, Folder 783)
  - Post-Doctoral Fee Account - 8700-1935-1974907 (Box 16, Folder 784)
  - Advisory Committee - Graduate School (Box 16, Folder 785)
  - Advisory Committee, Graduate School - Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 786)
  - Alumni Board #3 (Box 16, Folder 787)
  - Alumni Association National Meeting (Box 16, Folder 788)
  - Alumni Day Program Information (Box 16, Folder 789)
  - Alumni Fund Charts - Graduate and Professional Schools (Box 16, Folder 790)
  - Alumni House - Yale University (Box 16, Folder 791)
  - Alumni Magazine (Box 16, Folder 792)
  - Archives, Yale University (Box 16, Folder 793)
  - Basement Storage Lists (Box 16, Folder 794)
  - Office of the Business Manager (Box 16, Folder 795)
  - By-Laws (Box 16, Folder 796)
  - Communication Services (Box 16, Folder 797)
  - Office of the Comptroller (Box 16, Folder 798)
  - Corporation Votes (Box 16, Folder 799)
  - Dean's Directives (Box 16, Folder 800)
  - Directors of Graduate Study (Box 16, Folder 801)
  - Endowment Investment Policies (Box 16, Folder 802)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee on Library Problems, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 803)
  - F.A.S. Executive Committee (Box 16, Folder 804)
  - FAS Budget Projections, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 805)
  - Faculty Research Grant Committee (Box 16, Folder 806)
  - Faculty Research Grants, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 807)
  - Sub-Committee on Governance, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 808)
  - Graduate School
    - Executive Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 809)
    - Assistant Deanships (Box 16, Folder 810)
    - Association Awards (Box 16, Folder 811)
    - Association - Current (Box 16, Folder 812)
    - Proposal (Box 16, Folder 813)
    - Coat of Arms (Box 16, Folder 814)
    - Association Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 815)
    - Basement Inventory, 1966 July (Box 16, Folder 816)
    - Discipline Committee (Box 16, Folder 817)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 818)
    - Senate Committee (Box 16, Folder 819)
    - Senate Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 820)
  - Anthropology- Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 821)
  - Astronomy - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 822)
  - Biology - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 823)
  - Chemistry - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 824 - 825)
  - Economics - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 826)
  - Engineering and Applied Sciences - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 827)
  - Geology - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 828)
  - History - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 829)
  - Mathematics - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 830)
  - Miscellaneous - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 831)
  - Molecular Biophysics - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 832)
  - Psychology - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 833)
  - Physics - Personnel Profiles (Box 17, Folder 834 - 835)
  - Sociology - Personnel Files (Box 18, Folder 836)
  - Accreditation (Box 18, Folder 837)
  - African-American Institute (Box 18, Folder 838)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 18, Folder 839)
  - American Association of University Professors (Box 18, Folder 840)
  - American Association of University Women (Box 18, Folder 841)
  - American Council on Education (Box 18, Folder 842)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 18, Folder 843)
  - American Numismatic Society (Box 18, Folder 844)
  - ACLS - American Studies Fellows (Box 18, Folder 845)
  - American Telephone and Telephone Company (Box 18, Folder 846)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 18, Folder 847)
  - Association of American Universities (Box 18, Folder 848)
  - Audio-Visual Center (Box 18, Folder 849)
  - Bensinger Professorship Fund (Box 18, Folder 850)
  - Berkeley's Gift (Box 18, Folder 851)
  - Brown University - Post-Doctoral Fellowships (Box 18, Folder 852)
  - Career Advisory Office (Box 18, Folder 854)
  - Carnegie Fellows (Box 18, Folder 855)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 18, Folder 856)
  - Civil Affairs Training Program Certificate (Box 18, Folder 857)
  - College Scholarship Service (Box 18, Folder 858)
  - Commencement Program Requests (Box 18, Folder 859)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 18, Folder 860)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 18, Folder 861)
  - Community Relations (Box 18, Folder 862)
  - Computer in Humanities (Box 18, Folder 863)
  - Conference Board Association Research Council #3 (Box 18, Folder 864)
  - Connecticut College Program (Box 18, Folder 865)
  - Connecticut Educational Facilities Authority (Box 18, Folder 866)
  - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 18, Folder 867)
  - Connecticut State Scholarship Grant (Box 18, Folder 868)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1969- (Box 18, Folder 869)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 870)
  - CGS - "Graduate Study in the U.S.", 1966 (Box 18, Folder 871)
  - CGS Fellowship Date Material (Box 18, Folder 872)
  - DAAD (Box 18, Folder 873)
  - Danforth
    - Graduate Fellowships for Women, 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 874)
    - News and Notes, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 876)
    - Teaching Assistant Program - Directors of Graduate School Responses (Box 18, Folder 877)
  - Directory of Graduate Deans, HEW - Office of Education (Box 18, Folder 878)
  - Dwarf Studies, 1967 July 1 (Box 18, Folder 879)
  - Eastern Deans (Seven Dwarfs) T.R. File - Room 140 (Box 18, Folder 880)
  - Education and World Affairs (Box 18, Folder 881)
  - Educational Research - Burnham (Box 19, Folder 882)
  - Educational Testing Service #3 (Box 19, Folder 883)
  - ETS Matching Experiment, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 884)
  - Effort Reporting (Box 19, Folder 885)
  - Commission on Equal Opportunity (Box 19, Folder 886)
  - Fellowship Drive (Box 19, Folder 887)
  - Fellowship Policy - Columbia (Box 19, Folder 888)
  - Fire Regulations - Campus Police (Box 19, Folder 889)
  - Ford Humanities Project (Box 19, Folder 891)
  - Ford Interdisciplinary Fellowships (Box 19, Folder 892)
  - Free University - Berlin (Box 19, Folder 893)
  - General Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 894)
  - Government and University (Box 19, Folder 895)
  - Grading - Correspondence - Re: Policy and Procedures, etc (Box 19, Folder 896)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 897)
  - Harvard University (Box 19, Folder 898)
  - HEW Questionnaire, 1966 May (Box 19, Folder 899)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare -, 1966 January (Box 19, Folder 900)
  - HEW Cost Sharing in Research Grants (Box 19, Folder 901)
  - W. Press Hodgkins (Box 19, Folder 902)
  - Honors - to Yale Faculty (Box 19, Folder 903)
  - Howland Fellowships (Box 19, Folder 904)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 19, Folder 905)
  - International Business Machines Corporation, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 906)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 19, Folder 907)
  - International Conferences (Box 19, Folder 908)
  - International Office - Yale (Box 19, Folder 909)
  - Job Seekers, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 910)
  - Latin-American Exchange Program - University of Connecticut (Box 19, Folder 912)
  - Law School (Box 19, Folder 913)
  - Library - General (Box 19, Folder 914)
  - Library of Congress Material (Box 19, Folder 915)
  - Magdalen College Fellowship, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 916)
  - McCormick Fellows (Box 19, Folder 917)
  - NASA, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 920)
  - National Council - Teaching of English (Box 19, Folder 921)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 19, Folder 922)
  - National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council (Box 20, Folder 923)
  - National Institutes of Health (Box 20, Folder 924)
  - NIH Training Program - NIH and NSF Expense Allowance (Box 20, Folder 925)
  - NSF Organizational Directory (Box 20, Folder 926)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 20, Folder 927)
  - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 20, Folder 928)
  - New England Conference on Graduate Education (Box 20, Folder 929)
  - New England Institute (Box 20, Folder 930)
  - New Haven Public Schools - Experimental School (Box 20, Folder 931)
  - News Reports - Special Tr. File Room 140, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 932)
  - Dale Noble - Midwest Office, University Development (Box 20, Folder 933)
  - Office of Education (Box 20, Folder 934)
  - Professional Ethics (Box 20, Folder 936)
  - Research Assistants (Box 20, Folder 937)
  - John Scott Award (Box 20, Folder 939)
  - Selective Service Material (Box 20, Folder 940)
  - Senior Advisory Board Report (Box 20, Folder 941)
  - Senior Research Associates (Box 20, Folder 942)
  - Seven Dwarfs (Box 20, Folder 943)
  - State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (Box 20, Folder 946)
  - SNET Orders - Centrex Information (Box 20, Folder 948)
  - Petty Cash, 1964 September (Box 20, Folder 949)
  - Term Appointments Material (MH) (Box 20, Folder 950)
  - The Robert A. Taft Institute (Box 20, Folder 951)
  - Title II (Ashton and Moore) (Box 20, Folder 952)
  - Title IV - General Information (Box 20, Folder 953)
  - Record of Transfer File (Box 20, Folder 954)
  - Title V Application (Box 20, Folder 955)
  - Title IV, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 956)
  - Teaching Material (Box 20, Folder 957)
  - University Computer Administration Committee (Box 20, Folder 958)
  - Office of University Development (Box 20, Folder 959)
  - Urban Studies and Programs - J. Fleishman (Box 20, Folder 960)
  - U.S. Government Programs (Box 20, Folder 961)
  - Veterans - Certificate of Eligibility, etc (Box 20, Folder 962)
  - Vitae - Potential Academic Administrators (Box 20, Folder 963)
  - Wallace Affair (Box 20, Folder 964)
  - Western Office, Yale University - Frank W. Schork, Director (Box 20, Folder 965)
  - Woodrow Wilson Lists (Box 20, Folder 966)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowships (Box 21, Folder 967)
  - Woodrow Wilson Teaching Internship Program (Box 21, Folder 968)
  - Yale College - General (Box 21, Folder 969)
  - Yale College Courses (Box 21, Folder 970)